<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Hefei Mei</title>
    <link>https://example.com/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research on the Interpretability of Object Detection Networks</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/interpretable/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/interpretable/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This paper completes the interpretative model of Score-CAM method on the Fast R-CNN network, and outputs the saliency map of the high impact area for each detection frame of the network. By observing the distribution of saliency degree, this paper proposes that the high saliency degree of detection frame contains both decision score information and frame location information. By detecting the outward extension of the detection frame when the objects are adjacent to each other, the relationship between the frame location and the high saliency degree inside the frame is verified by the way of frame shrinkage, which provides a theoretical basis for the optimization of the detection location using the class activation saliency map.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distance measurement of objects in overlapping fields of view using binocular cameras based on MATLAB</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/measurement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/measurement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article develops a code implementation for ranging objects in overlapping fields of view using a binocular camera in the MATLAB environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The overall architecture of this article is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on the provided calibration images, use the Stereo Camera Calibrator toolbox in MATLAB to calibrate the internal and external parameters of the left and right cameras.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using the parameters obtained in the first step, remove the distortion of the left and right ranging images.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perform Bouguet polar correction to convert non parallel binocular systems into aligned parallel binocular systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a parallel binocular system, select the same pixel on the left and right images and use the ranging formula to calculate the distance&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research on Visual Object Tracking Technology</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/tracking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project focuses on target tracking under the Siamese network framework, and achieves high-precision target tracking algorithms in complex backgrounds by optimizing the network. The current project mainly focuses on the implementation of target tracking algorithms based on the deep twin network SiamFC. Relevant filtering is added to the pre trained CNN features, combining the excellent offline discrimination ability of CNN with the effective online learning ability of CF to complete the implementation of CFNet network.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
